(Raj:)And just for the record,
(Raj:)labradoodles are
hypo-allergenic,
(Raj:)which is a very sexy quality to
those troubled by animal dander.
AMY
So, what do you think?
(Sheldon:)It's a charming illusion,
but it does not cheer me up.
(Amy:)Not even when I do this?
(Leonard:)No.
(Amy:)Well, that was the last arrow
in my quiver of whimsy.
(Sheldon:)Do you realize that teaching
is the first thing
(Sheldon:)I've failed at
since my ill-fated attempt
(Sheldon:)to complete a chin-up
in March of 1989?
(Amy:)If this humiliating experience
(Amy:)is really troubling you,
(Amy:)there are things
we could do about it.
(Sheldon:)For instance?
(Amy:)Well, the first thing
that comes to mind
(Amy:)is isolating the part
of your brain
(Amy:)where the memory is stored
and destroying it with a laser.
(Sheldon:)Hmm, no.
(Sheldon:)One slip of the hand,
(Sheldon:)and suddenly I'm sitting
in the Engineering Department,